<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mobile Banking &#8211; Just Cash</title>
	<atom:link href="https://just.cash/tag/mobile-banking/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://just.cash</link>
	<description>the next Mobile Cash technology</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:22:20 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>See mobile cash in action!</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/see-mobile-cash-action/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Just Cash]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Cash Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ATM ISO's/IAD's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Convenience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App Integration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardless]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?p=361</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ve been reading a lot about mobile cash, powered by Just Cash. Ready to see it in action? Click here to see how it works! &#160; &#160;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/see-mobile-cash-action/">See mobile cash in action!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ve been reading a lot about mobile cash, powered by Just Cash. Ready to see it in action?</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/viK82KYEpqs"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-373" src="http://just.cash/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Screenshot-2016-11-22-15.59.57-279x300.png" alt="screenshot-2016-11-22-15-59-57" width="279" height="300" srcset="https://just.cash/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Screenshot-2016-11-22-15.59.57-279x300.png 279w, https://just.cash/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/Screenshot-2016-11-22-15.59.57.png 405w" sizes="(max-width: 279px) 100vw, 279px" /></a></p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/viK82KYEpqs" target="_blank">Click here</a> to see how it works!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/see-mobile-cash-action/">See mobile cash in action!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canadians not afraid to venture outside the big banks for financial products</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/canadians-not-afraid-venture-outside-big-banks-financial-products/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 19:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Just Cash]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Institutions]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?p=346</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Nearly one-third of Canadians have gone outside their banks in the past year for a financial services product or service, according to a new survey from EY. Add those who plan to “in the near future” and the figure climbs to more than 50 per cent, signaling the potential threat of rivals including upstart financial<a class="moretag" href="https://just.cash/canadians-not-afraid-venture-outside-big-banks-financial-products/"> Read More...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/canadians-not-afraid-venture-outside-big-banks-financial-products/">Canadians not afraid to venture outside the big banks for financial products</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Nearly one-third of Canadians have gone outside their banks in the past year for a financial services product or service, according to a new survey from EY.</p>
<div id="npAd1" class="ad" data-google-query-id="CPK2j5_d-88CFYcDPwod16MDTQ"></div>
<p>Add those who plan to “in the near future” and the figure climbs to more than 50 per cent, signaling the potential threat of rivals including upstart financial technology firms to key business lines within Canada’s banks.</p>
<p>“To stay relevant, especially as financial technology companies, or fintechs, are taking a piece of the market, traditional banks need to build on their strengths — including brand, trust and community presence,” said Paul Battista, financial services advisory leader at EY, the global consultancy formerly known as Ernst &amp; Young.&#8221;</p>
<p><a href="http://www.financialpost.com/m/wp/news/blog.html?b=business.financialpost.com/news/fp-street/canadians-not-afraid-to-venture-outside-the-big-banks-for-financial-products-ey-survey-finds&amp;pubdate=2016-10-23" target="_blank">Click here to continue to the full article.</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/canadians-not-afraid-venture-outside-big-banks-financial-products/">Canadians not afraid to venture outside the big banks for financial products</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>With same-day ACH looming, Dwolla unveils a payout feature for its white-label API</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/with-same-day-ach-looming-dwolla-unveils-a-payout-feature-for-its-white-label-api/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 20:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Just Cash]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trends]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App Integration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[API]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?p=190</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Companies that have been planning for months for the arrival Friday of same-day automated clearing house payments are getting ready to pounce, and one of the first opportunities lies in platform payouts. Des Moines, Iowa-based Dwolla Inc., for example, on Wednesday is announcing a new feature that marketplaces, gig economies, and payroll services can integrate<a class="moretag" href="https://just.cash/with-same-day-ach-looming-dwolla-unveils-a-payout-feature-for-its-white-label-api/"> Read More...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/with-same-day-ach-looming-dwolla-unveils-a-payout-feature-for-its-white-label-api/">With same-day ACH looming, Dwolla unveils a payout feature for its white-label API</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Companies that have been planning for months for the arrival Friday of same-day automated clearing house payments are getting ready to pounce, and one of the first opportunities lies in platform payouts. Des Moines, Iowa-based Dwolla Inc., for example, on Wednesday is announcing a new feature that marketplaces, gig economies, and payroll services can integrate to make same-day payouts <em>en masse</em> to service providers like drivers and care-givers.&#8221;</p>
<p><a href="http://www.digitaltransactions.net/news/story/With-Same-Day-ACH-Looming_-Dwolla-Unveils-a-Payout-Feature-for-its-White-Label-API" target="_blank">Click here to continue to the full article.</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/with-same-day-ach-looming-dwolla-unveils-a-payout-feature-for-its-white-label-api/">With same-day ACH looming, Dwolla unveils a payout feature for its white-label API</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>The secret, low-tech ingredient that mobile money needs to clinch customer satisfaction</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/the-secret-low-tech-ingredient-that-mobile-money-needs-to-clinch-customer-satisfaction/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 20:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Just Cash]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile Cash Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ATM ISO's/IAD's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App Integration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Institutions]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?p=195</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>“Increased governmental regulation, low interest rates, and an increasingly competitive marketplace have placed enormous pressure on banks to raise revenue from their existing customer base, while reducing the cost to serve their customers. Furthermore, the evolution of digital banking channels and the emergence of new customer segments, i.e., millennials, has impacted traditional methods of servicing<a class="moretag" href="https://just.cash/the-secret-low-tech-ingredient-that-mobile-money-needs-to-clinch-customer-satisfaction/"> Read More...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/the-secret-low-tech-ingredient-that-mobile-money-needs-to-clinch-customer-satisfaction/">The secret, low-tech ingredient that mobile money needs to clinch customer satisfaction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Increased governmental regulation, low interest rates, and an increasingly competitive marketplace have placed enormous pressure on banks to raise revenue from their existing customer base, while reducing the cost to serve their customers. Furthermore, the evolution of digital banking channels and the emergence of new customer segments, i.e., millennials, has impacted traditional methods of servicing customers and building relationships.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Those were the summary findings of the J.D. Power 2016 U.S. Retail Banking Satisfaction Study. This study, the 11th of its kind, measured customer satisfaction around six aspects of consumer banking: account information; channel activities; facility; fees; problem resolution; and product offerings. “Channel activities” included ratings of six separate channels for customer interaction: ATMs; branch offices; call centers; IVR; mobile apps; and banks’ websites.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A striking new finding in this study was that mobile banking appears to have had a direct impact on overall satisfaction. Overall satisfaction ratings were 27 points higher on average for customers who use mobile banking than among those who do not. The gap was even wider for those customer who were highly satisfied with their mobile experience.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the evolution and growth of mobile banking and payments, the demand for cash has remained study, and even has grown. Cash remains the most commonly used method of payment around the world, and 85% of Americans report that their use of cash has not dropped in recent years (according to a 2016 Mercator Advisory Group report.)</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These findings are not as squarely at odds as they first seem. Customers are demanding more flexibility and convenience from their bank, and high mobile adoption means they are willing to process transactions through their devices, if the app is intuitive and secure. But many transactions still involve a physical transfer of goods for cash. This means that customers are looking for ways in which their banking apps can be extended to safely access ATMs for withdrawals.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So ATMs are not going to leave the banking landscape anytime soon. While many pundits are predicting that mobile will “disrupt” or “eclipse” ATM use, the data tell a different story. A 2014 study from Visa found that more than half of respondents (57%) claimed that ATM convenience was their primary reason for choosing a financial institution. For the remaining 43%, many said it was the close second.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The more likely scenario, then, is that mobile offerings and ATMs will merge in the future to create a part-digital, part-physical integrated network. Until that happens, there is a looming market opportunity to collect more fees and drive customer satisfaction even higher.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/the-secret-low-tech-ingredient-that-mobile-money-needs-to-clinch-customer-satisfaction/">The secret, low-tech ingredient that mobile money needs to clinch customer satisfaction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mobile banking makes customers happier with their bank</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/mobile-banking-makes-customers-happier-with-their-bank/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 19:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Just Cash]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trends]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[App Integration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Institutions]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?p=185</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The growing number of Canadians who use their phones for banking are happier with their financial institutions — and not just because mobile banking is convenient, J.D. Power suggested Thursday. The market research company’s 2016 Canadian Retail Banking Satisfaction Study found customers who used a banking app reported an overall satisfaction score of 836 out<a class="moretag" href="https://just.cash/mobile-banking-makes-customers-happier-with-their-bank/"> Read More...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/mobile-banking-makes-customers-happier-with-their-bank/">Mobile banking makes customers happier with their bank</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The growing number of Canadians who use their phones for banking are happier with their financial institutions — and not just because mobile banking is convenient, J.D. Power suggested Thursday.</p>
<p>The market research company’s 2016 Canadian Retail Banking Satisfaction Study found customers who used a banking app reported an overall satisfaction score of 836 out of 1000, while those who didn’t had a satisfaction score of 760.&#8221;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thestar.com/business/2016/08/02/mobile-banking-makes-customers-happier-with-their-bank.html" target="_blank">Click here to continue to the full article.</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/mobile-banking-makes-customers-happier-with-their-bank/">Mobile banking makes customers happier with their bank</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
