<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Executive Officers &#8211; Just Cash</title>
	<atom:link href="https://just.cash/teammember/executive-officers/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://just.cash</link>
	<description>the next Mobile Cash technology</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:22:20 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Todd Lawrence</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/teammembers/executive-teammember/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 15:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marissa Solomon-Vickers]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?post_type=teammember&#038;p=218</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Todd is passionate problem-solver who values hard work, persistence, and patience. As CEO of Just Cash, he is primarily responsible for Just Cash&#8217;s vision and executing its mission. Todd has a decade of experience as an investment banking professional and entrepreneur in multiple countries and geographies. Todd has advised on over 25 diverse M&#38;A and corporate finance<a class="moretag" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/executive-teammember/"> Read More...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/executive-teammember/">Todd Lawrence</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Todd is passionate problem-solver who values hard work, persistence, and patience. As CEO of Just Cash, he is primarily responsible for Just Cash&#8217;s vision and executing its mission.</p>
<p>Todd has a decade of experience as an investment banking professional and entrepreneur in multiple countries and geographies. Todd has advised on over 25 diverse M&amp;A and corporate finance assignments and was previously the Chief Financial Officer and early investor in a private mining company where he continues to provide on-going strategic advice.</p>
<p>Todd graduated from Brock University with a Bachelor of Business Administration (Honours) Concentration in Finance (Co-op Option) degree and spent a semester in Rouen, France studying international business and finance at Institut de Formation Internationale. Todd is an active mentor for Brock&#8217;s Undergraduate and Masters students.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/executive-teammember/">Todd Lawrence</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Victor Cook</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/teammembers/261/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 21:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Oppelt]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?post_type=teammember&#038;p=261</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Victor Cook is the CTO for Just Cash and architect of its patent pending system. He has been innovating for most of his 25 year career. Starting with a technical foundation in the early 1990&#8217;s he started, grew and sold an Internet consulting firm. From there he partnered with a physician to bring the first touch<a class="moretag" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/261/"> Read More...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/261/">Victor Cook</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Victor Cook is the CTO for Just Cash and architect of its patent pending system. He has been innovating for most of his 25 year career. Starting with a technical foundation in the early 1990&#8217;s he started, grew and sold an Internet consulting firm. From there he partnered with a physician to bring the first touch screen computerized prescription system to hundreds of US emergency departments. Victor gained international experience as he led development of the largest real estate multiple listing service in Brazil.  He has also worked with tele-medicine, big data analytics and interfaces for clinical HL7 and billing and payment EDI. Victor earned his B.S. from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and M.S. from the University of Florida.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/261/">Victor Cook</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marcus Sowinski</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/teammembers/marcus-sowinski/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 21:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olivia Oppelt]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?post_type=teammember&#038;p=265</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Marcus Sowinski is Partner and COO at Just Cash. He has been leading startup companies to success for more than a decade, working in diverse fields such as healthcare technology, medical billing, software development, mobile applications, and regulatory compliance. Marcus’s roots are firmly in developing software technologies. Together with a fellow Just Cash partner, Marcus<a class="moretag" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/marcus-sowinski/"> Read More...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/marcus-sowinski/">Marcus Sowinski</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Marcus Sowinski is Partner and COO at Just Cash. He has been leading startup companies to success for more than a decade, working in diverse fields such as healthcare technology, medical billing, software development, mobile applications, and regulatory compliance. </span></p>
<p>Marcus’s roots are firmly in developing software technologies. Together with a fellow Just Cash partner, Marcus helped deliver a cutting-edge electronic prescription system to emergency room physicians across the country. Throughout his career, Marcus has guided a variety of businesses to profitability through roles such as CIO, COO, President, and Chairman, often managing multimillion-dollar budgets and a wide array of customer and marketing initiatives.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Marcus holds a bachelor of science degree in Management of Information Systems with a minor in Project Management from the University of Central Florida School of Business. Marcus brings with him an energizing approach to driving success and reaching new goals for Just Cash.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/marcus-sowinski/">Marcus Sowinski</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Luis Ruggiero</title>
		<link>https://just.cash/teammembers/luis-ruggiero/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 15:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marissa Solomon-Vickers]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://just.cash/?post_type=teammember&#038;p=213</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Luis Ruggiero is partner and Strategy &#38; International for Just Cash. Luis brings wisdom, discernment and perception to the vision, mission and values of the company. With international experience in the retail industry &#8211; as executive of a top multinational company and as entrepreneur &#8211; Luis adds new perspectives to the company&#8217;s goals and strategies. He has built a strong background in<a class="moretag" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/luis-ruggiero/"> Read More...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/luis-ruggiero/">Luis Ruggiero</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Luis Ruggiero is partner and Strategy &amp; International for Just Cash. <span class="s1">Luis brings wisdom, discernment and perception to the vision, mission and values of the company. With international experience in the retail industry &#8211; as executive of a top multinational company and as entrepreneur &#8211; Luis adds new perspectives to the company&#8217;s goals and strategies. He has built a strong background in business strategy, business development, marketing and customer relations, along his almost 30 years career; a background that only strengthens his natural ability to identify potential business opportunities.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Luis has worked in Brazil, Peru and the USA. He is a graduate from Ottawa University, Ottawa, KS, with major in Business Administration. He also graduated from Rhema Bible Training Center, Sao Paulo, Brazil.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash/teammembers/luis-ruggiero/">Luis Ruggiero</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://just.cash">Just Cash</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
